<contexts>

  <context id="scdDialog" title="SCD Dialog">
    <description>Scd Dialog</description>   
  </context>
   <context id="unused" title="Unused fields">
    <description>Unused fields are coming from the previous component by auto propagation.</description>    
  </context>
  <context id="surrogateKey" title="Surrogate key">
    <description>Select the column where the generated surrogate key will be stored. A surrogate key can be generated based on a method  selected on the Creation list.
Select the method to be used for the key generation: 
input field: key is provided in an input field. 
routine: you can access the basic functions through Ctrl+ Space bar combination. 
table max +1: the maximum value from the SCD table is incremented to create a surrogate key. 
sequence/identity: auto-incremental key.</description>    
  </context>
  
   <context id="sourceKey" title="Source key">
    <description>Select one or more columns to be used as key,  to ensure the unicity of incoming data.</description>    
  </context>
  
  <context id="type0" title="Use SCD Type 0 fields">
    <description>Use type 0</description>    
  </context>
  
  <context id="type1" title="Use SCD Type 1 fields">
    <description>Use the type 1 if change tracking is not necessary. SCD Type 1 should be used for typos corrections for example. Select the columns of the schema, that will be checked for changes.</description>    
  </context>
    
  <context id="type2" title="Use SCD Type 2 fields">
    <description>Use type 2 if changes need to be tracked down. SCD Type 2 should be used to trace updates for example. Select the columns of the schema, that will be 
checked for changes. Start date: Adds a column to your SCD schema to hold the start date. You can select one of the input schema column as Start Date in the SCD table.  
End Date: Adds a column to your SCD schema to hold the end date value for the record. When the record is currently active, the End date show a null 
value or you can select Fixed Year value and fill in with a fictive year  to avoid having a null value in the End date field. 
Log Active Status: Adds a column to your  SCD schema to hold the true or false status value. This column helps to spot easily the active record. 
Log versions: Adds a column to your SCD schema to hold the version number of the record.</description>    
  </context>
  
   <context id="type3" title="Use SCD Type 3 fields">
    <description>Use type 3 when you want to keep track of the previous value of a changing column Current value field: Select the column where the 
changing value is tracked down. Previous value field: Select the column where the previous value should be stored.</description>    
  </context>  
  
</contexts>
